Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers, Inclusive: 1884-1928, Bulk: 1917-1927
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers
Inclusive: 1884-1928, Bulk: 1917-1927
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3971
Unknown
4 document boxes and 2 OVZ boxes
The Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers contain small bound ledger books kept by Washington County landowners.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Poor.
Biography/Profile
The name(s) of the landowner(s) were not recorded.
Scope and Content
The Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers include small bound ledger books with handwritten amounts the tenant farmers owed to landowners in Washington County, Texas, 1884-1928. Names of tenant farmers are written on each page that documents their payments, but the name of the landowner is not recorded.
Arrangement
The Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers were in an unorganized stack in a single record storage box prior to this finding aid. Currently, the Washington County Tenant Farm ledgers are arranged in one series: I. Financial Documents.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3971. Acquired 2010-04-29
Index Terms
Places
Washington County (Tex.)
Genres
Financial records.
- Financial Documents, 1884-1928; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Poor.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains ledger books with handwritten amounts that tenant farmers owed to landowners in Washington County, Texas. This series is in poor condition.
  - Ledgers, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ledgers, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ledgers, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ledgers, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ledgers, 1903 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1905 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1906 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Ledgers, 1911 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers, 1913 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Ledgers, 1914 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Ledgers, 1915 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1927 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Ledgers, 1928 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 3)